morning and good evening good afternoon
早上好，晚上好，下午
wherever you may be and welcome to the
无论您身在何处，都欢迎来到
spring webinar program I am Peter
春季网络研讨会计划我是Peter
Humphrey do Bell for marketing for
汉弗莱·杜·贝尔（Humphrey do Bell）用于营销
spring and Cloud Foundry I work at
我在Spring和Cloud Foundry工作
pivotal and I am delighted to introduce
关键的，我很高兴介绍
you today if you haven't seen heard from
你今天，如果你还没有听到过
him before um Michael fluid who's going
在迈克尔·弗洛伊德之前，他要去
to talk about domain-driven design
谈论领域驱动的设计
Michael with no further ado are really
迈克尔，事不宜迟
excited to have you back
高兴您回来
frequent spring lawn speakers so welcome
经常春季草坪演讲者，欢迎
back and um yeah let's let's dive right
回来，嗯，让我们潜水吧
into it curious to hear about what you
好奇地听到你的声音
what you have so for us today okay thank
您今天对我们有什么好处，谢谢
you very much Peter for the kind
彼得，您非常友善
introduction and welcome everybody to
介绍并欢迎大家
joining me on this webinar on a topic
与我一起参加有关主题的网络研讨会
that I would say is getting quite a high
我会说越来越高
priest and he again because the main
牧师和他再次因为主要
room design isn't something very new it
房间设计不是什么新鲜事物
originated back in I think it was 2003
起源于我认为那是2003年
with the excellent book by Eric event
与埃里克事件的优秀书
and with the writing of the idea of
并写下了
self-contained systems or micro services
独立的系统或微服务
the main room design really had another
主房间的设计真的有另一个
push in the community in my eyes today
今天在我的眼中推动社区
I'm going to talk about strategic design
我将谈论战略设计
which is I would say one of the major
我想说这是主要的
chapters in the book that has a very
书中的章节
very high relevance to the whole idea
与整个想法的相关性很高
and the concept of micro services room
和微服务室的概念
and I'm going to cut this webinar today
我今天要剪掉这个网络研讨会
basically in let's say two parts and the
基本上可以说分为两个部分
first part I will include to you the
第一部分，我将向您介绍
idea of strategic design what strategic
战略设计的思想是什么战略
design is all about we're going to talk
设计就是我们要谈论的全部
about bounded context we're going to
关于有限上下文，我们将要
talk about context Maps and the mapping
谈论上下文映射和映射
patterns in the context map and after
上下文映射中和之后的模式
that we're going to take a look
我们来看看
especially at the context mapping
特别是在上下文映射时
part with over an example landscape
部分与示例景观
application landscape has been written
编写了应用程序格局
with spring boot and it has to do
用 spring boot ，它必须做
something about this truck who is a very
关于这辆卡车，他是一个非常
business driven book and don't be afraid
业务驱动的书，不要害怕
I'm not going to show you another text
我不会再给你显示文字
or or another pet shop with that example
或其他带有该示例的宠物店
but let's start with introducing myself
但让我们先自我介绍
my name is Mike retreat I work for a
我的名字叫迈克务虚会
company called in OQ I'm a principal
公司叫OQ我是校长
consultant and I usually do a lot of
顾问，我通常会做很多
stuff around spring I did a couple of
我在春季前后做了几件事
talks at the spring one conference have
春季会议上的演讲有
already done a webinar for the pivotal
已经为关键会议做了网络研讨会
folks surrounding spring and you can
乡亲周围的 Spring ，你可以
follow me on twitter my handle is
在Twitter上关注我，我的处理方式是
athlete boss and I will also show share
运动员老板，我也将展示份额
links to the code and the slides right
链接到代码和正确的幻灯片
after a talk on my Twitter account but
在我的Twitter帐户上讨论之后，但是
the first thing is you can also check
首先是你也可以检查
out all the code for the application
列出应用程序的所有代码
landscape I'm going to show on github
我将在github上展示的风景
but don't be shocked it's not a best
但不要震惊，这不是最好的
practice code and why that is the case
练习代码，为什么会这样
please read the readme to that very
请仔细阅读自述文件
carefully it is because I want to
小心是因为我想
demonstrate a couple of the patterns
展示几种模式
that you can see when you draw a context
绘制上下文时可以看到的
map of an application landscape before
之前的应用程序环境图
getting into the content I really have
进入我真正拥有的内容
to say that I didn't invent anything of
说我没有发明任何东西
that I'm a huge fan of the ideas that
我是这些想法的忠实粉丝
Eric evens and also won't learn and a
埃里克（Eric）偶也不会学习，
lot of other people in the DDD community
DDD社区中的很多其他人
have written down and if you haven't
写下了，如果你还没有
bought the books yet I can highly
买了书，但是我可以
recommend to you to buy Eric events book
推荐给您购买Eric活动书
on the main room design long learners
在主室设计长期学习者
book domain to design this build or
书域来设计此版本或
implementing domain clean design these
实施领域清洁设计这些
are absolutely great books and let's be
绝对是很棒的书，让我们成为
sure they they will last a very
确保他们会持续很长时间
long time in your bookshelf Eric's book
在书架上很长时间Eric的书
is now over I think 12 or 13 years old
现在已经结束了，我认为是12或13岁
already so and we're still talking about
已经如此，我们仍在谈论
this topic basically the heart of the
这个话题基本上是
main room design the main room design
主房间设计主房间设计
isn't basically only about let's say the
基本上不只是说
internal building blocks that we have
我们拥有的内部构件
been talking a lot about let's say in
谈论很多，让我们在
the early half of the year 2000 and also
2000年上半年以及
the big half of the year 2000 the
2000年上半年
internal building blocks there were a
内部构建块有一个
lot of now really well-known patterns
现在很多非常知名的模式
like the entity the value object and the
像实体一样，值对象和
repository so if you for instance take a
存储库，因此，例如，如果您采用
look at the spring data stuff you will
看看你会得到的 spring data
find an ad repository annotation and you
找到一个广告资源注释，然后
will also see a couple of a lot of the
还会看到很多
ideas from the repository pattern from
来自仓库模式的想法来自
the main room design implement it
主房间设计实现
directly into spring data and the main
直接进入Spring 数据和主
room design also consists of a part
房间设计也包括一部分
called strategic design I won't dwell
被称为战略设计，我不会住
into strategic design right now because
现在进入战略设计，因为
this is the major part of the
这是
presentation of this webinar I am going
我要参加的这个网络研讨会的演示
to deliver right now and another part of
立即交付和另一部分
the book were on large scale structure
这本书是大规模的结构
so basically how do you glow with the
所以基本上你如何用
main room design how do you go ahead and
主房间设计您如何进行和
grow application and also very important
增加应用程序也很重要
here is the part of the destination how
这是目的地的一部分
do I go ahead and distill stuff from a
我要继续从中提取东西吗
grown application into some smaller
成长为更小的应用程序
chunks and when we take a look
块，当我们看一看
especially at the part of strategic
特别是在战略方面
design and the destination part and we
设计和目标部分，我们
will see that a lot of these ideas that
将会看到很多这样的想法
have been sketched out in the early
早已被勾勒出来
2000s
2000年代
now match very very good on the idea
现在在这个想法上非常匹配
surrounding
周围
cloud native applications protector
云原生应用程序保护器
application and especially on the idea
应用，尤其是想法
surrounding micro services and
周围的微服务和
self-contained systems and in my eyes
自成体系，在我眼中
and that is something I actually wonder
这是我真正想知道的
quite a bit about is that a lot of the
相当多的是，
people in the micro services community
微服务社区中的人们
discuss let's say structuring micro
讨论让我们说微结构化
services along bounded context that is
沿有限上下文的服务
very true and this is a really an is a
非常真实，这确实是一个
major driver for really independent
真正独立的主要动力
independently and quickly deployable
独立且可快速部署
micro services but um let's be honest
微服务，但让我们说实话
among us we're now in this webinar
我们之中，我们现在参加了这次网络研讨会
not everybody is writing green print
不是每个人都在写绿色印刷
applications right now I mean if I take
现在的申请，我的意思是如果我参加
a look at a lot of my customers that I'm
看了很多我的客户
consulting they have a very strong set
咨询他们有很强的一套
of grown applications where they have
他们拥有的增长中的应用程序
invested millions and millions of euros
投资了数百万欧元
or dollars in them and you can't just go
或美元在里面，你不能只是去
ahead for a custom entry but go ahead
进行自定义输入，但继续进行
and shut down that application let's
并关闭该应用程序，让我们
rewrite it from scratch I mean that
从头开始重写它，我的意思是
would be a very career limiting move to
将是一个非常职业限制的举动
do so we have to be a little bit smaller
这样做我们必须小一点
and we have to see how we can eventually
我们必须看看我们最终如何
go ahead and take these applications
继续并接受这些申请
apart analyze the applications analyze
分开分析应用分析
the language and identify parts that we
语言并确定我们所需要的部分
can isolate and crease outwards through
可以隔离并向外折皱
instance micro services and this is
实例微服务，这是
exactly where especially the context
恰好在上下文中
mapping part of strategic design really
真正绘制战略设计的一部分
helps us and strategic design consists
帮助我们，战略设计包括
of I would say two major things the main
我会说两件事主要
driver is the bounded context and this
驱动程序是有限的上下文
is I would say the central part to
我想说的是
strategic design but there is also the
战略设计，但也有
context map which is a a means to
上下文映射是指
describe and to scale
描述并按比例
out an application landscape and along
找出应用程序环境
that context map you will see various I
那个背景图，你会看到各种各样的我
don't want to call them integration
不想称他们为整合
pattern but I'm going I would like to
模式，但我要去
say call them interaction models between
说他们之间的互动模型
systems and teams and let's go ahead and
系统和团队，让我们继续前进，
pick into this part of strategic design
参与战略设计的这一部分
so let's first off I'll go ahead and
所以首先让我继续
take a look at the boundary context the
看一下边界上下文
boundary context is basically something
边界上下文基本上是
that that every sophisticated business
那每一个复杂的业务
domain consists of a bunch of bound
域由一束束缚组成
context so for instance if you have a
上下文，例如，如果您有一个
mortgage loan application you can easily
您可以轻松申请抵押贷款
identify a couple of parts in these
找出其中的几个部分
applications for instance a part where
例如应用程序的一部分
you apply for a mortgage loan a part
您申请抵押贷款的一部分
where the bank is going to score you're
银行会在哪里给您评分
a player mortgage loan application where
玩家抵押贷款申请
they say yeah we're giving the loan to
他们说是的，我们正在贷款给
Michael for instance let's have him buy
例如迈克尔，让我们买他
a house depending on a couple of
一所房子取决于
criteria then there is a part where we
标准，然后有一部分，我们
have for instance a credit decision
例如有信用决定
where the management of the bank goes
银行的管理去向
ahead and said yes let's go for a loan
向前说，是的，让我们贷款
or now let's rather not give a loan to
或者现在我们宁愿不要贷款给
the to the person applying for it and
给申请者的
finally we have a a repayment so these
最后我们有还款，所以这些
are founded context and and the boundary
被建立的背景和边界
context contains models I mean the model
上下文包含模型我的意思是模型
is something that is being described in
被描述为
the internal building blocks of
的内部构件
domain-driven design so there you have
域驱动的设计，因此您可以
your entities your value objects your
您的实体，您的价值对象
aggregate your repositories your
汇总您的存储库
services your factories and they may
为您的工厂提供服务，他们可能
also issue the main events flow and the
还发布主要事件流和
most important part about the
关于最重要的部分
understanding of the construct of the
对结构的理解
boundary context in that is it is the
边界环境就是
boundary for the meaning of
边界的含义
given model and that is something that
给定模型，那是
[Music]
[音乐]
goes a little bit against the grain of
有点反对
for instance ideas like service-oriented
例如面向服务的想法
architectures or stuff that he's been
他去过的建筑或东西
doing in the last couple of years where
在最近几年里，
we tried to let's say centralize
我们试图说集中
meanings of models I'm from Germany and
我来自德国和
in Germany and there was a huge trend
在德国，有一个巨大的趋势
quite a few years ago and called the
相当多年前，并称为
Sultana meant that model the enterprise
苏丹娜的意思是为企业建模
company-wide data model where
公司范围内的数据模型
organizations tried to centralize the
组织试图集中
meanings of given models and well and
给定模型的含义以及
let's be fair it failed I don't know any
公平地说，失败了，我什么都不知道
company at all that really succeeded
真正成功的公司
with such a centralized definition of a
这样的集中定义
meaning of a model and basically if we
模型的含义，基本上，如果我们
if we take a look what we've been doing
如果我们看看我们一直在做什么
in our industry for the last couple of
在我们行业的最后两个
years and we've been fighting back and
几年来，我们一直在反击，
forth with centralized models or don't
集中式模型还是没有
we go ahead and go for decentralized
我们继续去分散
model nothing if we take a look at the
如果我们看看
ideas around micro services we will
关于微服务的想法，我们将
obviously see a strong tendency for a
显然看到了
strong decentralization because we want
强烈的权力下放，因为我们想要
independence we want to be able to
我们希望能够独立
deploy components independently once you
一旦您独立部署组件
be able to deploy one sprinkled
能够部署一个洒
application very often during a day but
一天中经常申请
we don't want to attack as a team with
我们不想与
that and in order to get through a
并且为了通过
better glimpse or a better grip on the
更好地瞥见或更好地把握
meaning of bounded context let's take a
有界上下文的含义让我们来
look at any campus I guess a lot of
看看任何一个校园，我猜很多
folks of you know the really awesome
你们中的人知道真的很棒
spring one conference which is going to
春季会议即将举行
take place in San Francisco this year or
今年在旧金山举行
for instance for the Europeans the
例如欧洲人
absolutely amazing spring i/o conference
春季I / O大会绝对精彩
which is a community driven comfort
这是社区带来的舒适感
surrounding everything spring which
周围的一切 Spring
takes place in Barcelona and these
发生在巴塞罗那，这些
conferences obviously need some software
会议显然需要一些软件
to management management and I have
进行管理，我有
identified a very simple let's say on
确定了一个非常简单的假设
the context model for these console
这些控制台的上下文模型
policy so there are some reservations we
政策，所以我们有些保留
have some event management context and
有一些事件管理环境
then you know it from every conference
那你每次会议都知道
everybody's running around with a badge
每个人都带着徽章跑来跑去
around their neck and this stuff needs
在他们脖子上，这东西需要
to be printed and done as well and now
现在也要打印和完成
we have a customer coming in to the
我们有一个客户来
conference but wants to attend the
会议，但想参加
spring loan conference and I mean the
春季贷款会议，我的意思是
customer if let's say I want to go to
客户，如果我想去
one of the conference that's me I'm
我是我的会议之一
standing there but let's take a look at
站在那儿，让我们看一下
how we see the customer in the
我们如何看待客户
reservations context the reservation
保留上下文保留
context I would say we have a rather
我会说我们有一个相当
natural modeling view on the customer so
对客户的自然建模观点
they have a name there's some payment
他们有一个名字有一些付款
details there's an address the customer
详细信息有客户地址
works at a specific company I mean this
在特定的公司工作我的意思是
is a model that is I would say very true
是一个模型，我会说很真实
to a lot of CRM or whatever applications
到很多CRM或任何其他应用程序
the interesting thing is how we see
有趣的是我们如何看待
these let's please put that in quotes
这些让我们用引号
the customer in the context of event
事件中的客户
management there basically we we don't
那里的管理基本上我们不
see the customer the way she or he
以他或他的方式看客户
stands in front of us basically the
基本上站在我们面前
customer can be seen as a lunch
客户可以看作是午餐
preference so I as a visible
偏好，所以我作为一个可见
circumference get reduced to a whatever
圆周变小
crappy lunch preference I'm a vegetarian
午餐偏爱我是素食主义者
and a meat-eater I'm a vegan
食肉者我是素食主义者
or whatever so we don't see in this
或其他任何我们看不到的东西
context a custom
风俗习惯
we see a meat-eater we see a vegetarian
我们看到食肉者，我们看到素食者
we see a vegan or somebody who wants
我们看到素食主义者或想要的人
kosher food or whatever so it's
犹太洁食或其他
basically you don't see the customer in
基本上你看不到顾客
the event management basically a lunch
活动管理基本上是午餐
product and we also want to see for
产品，我们也希望看到
instance in this case who wants to
在这种情况下谁想要
attend which sessions for instance is
参加例如哪个会议
Juergen challah is giving a talk at the
于尔根·查拉（Juergen challah）在
spring one conference and see one of the
春季会议，看看其中之一
original founders of Spring Framework
Spring Framework的原始创始人
the obviously getting a lot of attention
显然引起了很多关注
a lot of people want to go there on the
很多人想去那里
other hand if I do one of my talks
另一方面，如果我做我的一个演讲
maybe people say ah now he's not a part
也许人们说啊，现在他不参与了
of the spring team I'm going to skip out
The Spring Team 的成员，我将跳过
on Michael there's just a few
在迈克尔身上，只有几个
registration for that so they're
为此注册
basically a customer isn't a customer
基本上客户不是客户
it's a an amount of sessional
会期
registrations of interest for giving
给予感兴趣的注册
sessions for giving talks so that the
会议进行演讲，以便
organizer can scale the rooms
组织者可以缩放房间
let's put Jurgen into the the big big
让我们把尤尔根（Jurgen）变成大人物
big room and let's put Michael into a
大房间，让我们把迈克尔放在
small tiny room for whatever 20 people
小小的房间，可容纳20人
or something fana and then they ever
或一些法纳，然后他们曾经
interesting case with the badges to key
带钥匙徽章的有趣案例
in the benches we don't see the
在长凳上，我们看不到
customized lot the central model in the
定制批次的中心模型
batches is the badge basically me as a
批次基本上是我的徽章
customer I get reduced to a lunch
顾客我减少到午餐
preference and finally I get reduced to
偏好，最后我沦落为
a printed piece of paper so where I have
一张打印好的纸，所以我有
my name and they chopped description and
我的名字，他们砍了描述，
for instance my Twitter handle and
例如我的Twitter句柄和
pit-boss
上司
and so this takes into account that and
所以这考虑到了
we can basically work with some sort of
我们基本上可以与某种
a decentralized data and that is very
去中心化的数据
important
重要
decentralized behavior as well let me
分散的行为也让我
give you another example this was a
再举一个例子，这是一个
let's say a very data-centric example
假设一个非常以数据为中心的例子
another example is take a look at a car
另一个例子是看车
I'm not a very big cars guy personally I
我个人不是个大汽车人
want to get into a car turn it on and
想要开车进入并打开它
push the pedal to the metal as you say
如您所说，将踏板踩到金属上
in English I guess and and I want to
我想用英语我想
drive from A to B that's all I care
我要从A开车到B
about cars and on the other hand I have
关于汽车，另一方面
my service center and there's people
我的服务中心，有人
working in the service center and take a
在服务中心工作并接受
take a look at how they see the car if I
看看他们如何看我的车
model a car for the context my kelud
为我的环境建模汽车
usual user nothing special
普通用户没什么特别的
whatever take a look how you would model
随便看看你如何建模
the start the car hood of the car would
启动汽车的引擎盖会
you go ahead and say car get engine
你说汽车得到引擎
stocks start probably not you would
股票开始可能不是你会的
invoke a method card of start in that
调用start的方法卡
compass and the car knows how to start a
指南针，汽车知道如何启动
test because there's a couple of other
测试，因为还有其他两个
systems the GPS subsystem navigation
系统GPS子系统导航
infotainment and whatever you you have
信息娱乐，无论您拥有什么
ABS system is P and and whatnot in the
ABS系统是P，而在
cars so the car knows ok I need to start
汽车，所以汽车知道好了，我需要开始
the engine I need to start the light
我需要启动引擎的引擎
system I need to start the GPS subsystem
系统我需要启动GPS子系统
and whatever card knows that it's hidden
而任何卡知道它被隐藏
from me and a quick hint on a for you
从我这里快速提示给您
guys and if you want to monitor the
伙计们，如果你想监视
quality there's basically a nice law
质量基本上有一个很好的法则
called law of demeter out there and that
叫得住耳鼻喉的律法
helps you to identify such cases where
帮助您识别此类情况
you eventually have a model that doesn't
您最终拥有的模型没有
fit really nicely so the context you're
非常合适，因此您所处的环境
in so it will go too far for the given
在给定的情况下它会太过分了
time frame of that presentation to dig
该演示文稿的时间表
deep into the law of demeter but
深入到得克萨斯律法
eventually if you're interested in as
最终，如果您对
Coulier you'll find a lot of examples
还可以找到很多示例
about going back to the context with the
关于与
car let's go to the service center the
车，我们去服务中心
service center sees the technical person
服务中心见技术人员
in the service center is repairing your
服务中心正在修理您的
car see
车看
totally differently they may start the
他们可能完全不同地开始
engine in an isolated way they may start
以孤立的方式启动引擎
the infotainment system without the rest
没有其余部分的信息娱乐系统
of the system in order to be able to
为了能够
debug the car to repair it and whatever
调试汽车以对其进行维修
so you have a total different view on
所以您对
the car and you can go in further if you
车，如果您可以走得更远
go to the factory and you take a look at
去工厂，你看看
how they see the car this is also a
他们怎么看车，这也是
proble different view of the car now
现在对汽车的看法不同
let's pick up this example again with
让我们再次用这个例子
the reservation context conference so
预订上下文会议如此
each boundary context has its own model
每个边界上下文都有自己的模型
and its own view of a certain customer
以及对某些客户的看法
so we go from a very natural modeling of
所以我们从一个非常自然的模型
the customer to a lunch preference to a
顾客偏爱午餐
piece of paper basically and this is a
基本上是一张纸，这是一张
major and a blur for really independent
专业和模糊的真正独立
auto services if you really want to be
汽车服务，如果你真的想成为
able to deploy independently to give
能够独立部署
teams an empowerment of going away from
团队有权摆脱
a project thinking towards a product
考虑产品的项目
thinking this is a big big enabler
认为这是一个很大的推动者
because let's say the bench is team in
因为假设替补席是
my example one team and they write one
我的例子是一支球队，他们写一支
micro service for the budget they don't
他们没有预算的微服务
necessarily have to care about what's
一定要在乎什么
happening in the reservations and we
发生在保留，我们
have a choice by that of you if you take
如果您选择，请由您选择
a look at the name of the customer get
看客户的名字得到
the name in the reservations context and
预订上下文中的名称，以及
the benches so eventually we want share
板凳，所以最终我们要分享
data or we want to avoid shared data but
数据，或者我们要避免共享数据，但是
the good thing about that is we can make
这样做的好处是我们可以
an educated decision on that and
关于此的明智决定
basically in the centralized IT world
基本上在集中式IT世界中
the let's say the old-school enterprise
比方说老派企业
and he was you wanted of course the
他当然是你想要的
answer would have been of course we want
答案当然是我们想要的
to share data will be total catastrophe
共享数据将是一场大灾难
not having shared data here in this
在这里没有共享数据
point of view you can differ you can go
你可以去不同的角度去
and in a
并在
let's go separate ways right now talking
让我们现在分开谈谈
about separate way we conclude the next
关于单独的方式，我们总结下一个
part which is the context map and the
这是上下文映射和
context map is basically a say if you on
如果您在
the interaction between boundary context
边界语境之间的相互作用
because on the company side and says
因为在公司方面，并说
don't deliver a decent overview of the
不要提供关于
system because you don't know who is
系统，因为您不知道谁是谁
interacting with whom and how do they
与谁互动以及如何互动
interact and what and by introducing the
互动以及什么，并通过介绍
context map we go ahead and describe the
上下文图，我们继续描述
context between models and context and
模型与上下文之间的上下文以及
it is a very good starting point for
这是一个很好的起点
future transformation and let me be very
未来的转变，让我变得非常
clear here in my eyes the context map is
在我眼中清晰的上下文地图是
one of the really really shiny big gems
真正闪亮的大宝石之一
in the main room design why because if
在主房间设计为什么，因为
you take a look at how a lot of let's
你看看有多少让我们
say Enterprise architects sketch out or
说企业架构师画出草图或
model or through all the systems and you
建模或通过所有系统，您
will find out that most of these diagram
会发现这些图大部分
focus on it's a delivery relationships
专注于交付关系
or customer-supplier relationship system
或客户-供应商关系系统
a is calling service acts of system be
一个正在调用系统的服务行为是
the let's say mortgage application
假设抵押贷款申请
system is calling the scoring methods of
系统正在调用计分方法
the scoring system or something like
计分系统或类似的东西
that and I mean this is a very important
那，我的意思是，这是非常重要的
way scan to other system but in my eyes
扫描到其他系统但在我眼中
it holds a little bit short in one very
它合而为一
interesting thing and that is the fact
有趣的是，事实是
that these sorts of diagrams don't show
这些图不会显示
you what is happening with the models
你模型发生了什么
inside the consuming system so for
在消费系统内部
instance if you ask a credit agency for
例如，如果您要求信贷机构提供
a scoring of a given customer
给定客户的评分
you obviously get a model back from them
你显然从他们那里得到了一个模型
which is the scoring result now what is
现在是计分结果是什么
being done with the scoring Reza do you
用得分的Reza完成吗
store it in your own database the way it
将其存储在自己的数据库中
is you transform it or whatever this
你是在改造它还是其他
this isn't being explained in I would
这在我不会解释
say the typical enterprise architecture
说典型的企业架构
diagrams that we usually see and another
我们通常看到的图和另一个
thing that's also not being taken care
也没有得到照顾的事情
of is the way how certainties interact
确定性相互作用的方式
with each other let's say I'm very
彼此说我非常
honest there is no judgment on the
老实说，没有判断
political stance and behavior of a given
某人的政治立场和行为
T in a organization and this is exactly
T在一个组织中，这正是
what the context map displays it doesn't
上下文映射显示的内容不
just display call text or call
只显示通话文字或通话
relationships no it displayed also how
关系没有它也显示如何
this relationship is being lived out in
这种关系是活在
the corporation and mi I see the context
公司和我看到的上下文
map goes hand in hand with Conway's law
地图与康韦定律齐头并进
and let's dig a little bit into it and
让我们深入研究一下
the context map usually starts with an
内容映射通常以
existing system with the existing
现有系统
application so you know I've rarely seen
应用程序，所以你知道我很少见
people drawing a context context map in
人们在其中绘制上下文上下文图
a green field approach you usually have
您通常有一个绿色领域的方法
a system or a couple of systems that
一个或几个系统
interact with each other and you go
彼此互动，你去
ahead and analyze them and then you
继续分析它们，然后你
throw out context and there are a couple
扔掉上下文，有几个
of patterns are being defined in Eric's
模式的定义在Eric的
and Wong's books and it's basically
和黄的书，基本上
seven of them and please don't be
他们七个，请不要
mistaken by the name pattern when I say
我说的时候被名字模式弄错了
that some of these things for instance
例如，其中一些东西
the shared code and to which I'll get to
共享代码，我将去
you in a in a minute and something that
您在一分钟之内
a lot of you when you see again when I
很多人，当你再次见到我时
explain to you would feel pretty awkward
向你解释会觉得很尴尬
with implementing in a green
以绿色实现
in approach but it is basically stuff
在方法上，但基本上是东西
that happened in real world system and
发生在现实世界的系统中
that I see quite a bit in customer
我看到很多顾客
situations that I'm in so it's not a say
我所处的情况，所以这不是一句话
upfront design kind of thing it's more a
前期设计的东西更多的是
little analysis method are you how you
小分析方法你如何
can take a look at given system and how
可以看看给定的系统以及如何
you rate relationships between context
您评估上下文之间的关系
now let's begin - all these patterns and
现在开始-所有这些模式和
start with the share combo
从共享组合开始
the share Colonel says that two T's or
上校说两个T或
two bounded content share a subset of
两个有界内容共享一个子集
the domain model including the code and
包含代码的领域模型和
eventually the database and that is
最终是数据库，那就是
something for instance if we take a
例如，如果我们采取
technical look if we use let's say some
如果我们使用技术外观，让我们说一些
old-school binary protocols such as
老式的二进制协议，例如
Hessian or RMI or old-school eg gear
粗麻布或RMI或较老的齿轮
amore and promoting you usually have
和更多的提升你通常有
your meta clients all files or client
您的元客户端所有文件或客户端
class files somewhere
类文件在某处
lying around and each system relies on
躺在周围，每个系统都依赖
them on a binary level and eventually
他们在二进制级别，最终
there's behavior in there there's data
那里有数据
in there and this is a very tight leash
在那里，这是一个非常紧的皮带
add kernel between the two so obviously
在两者之间添加内核如此明显
you can't change anything in one system
您无法在一个系统中进行任何更改
without changing the other system as
而不更改其他系统
well but please be aware with the share
好吧，但是请注意分享
column it's not just about let's say
专栏不只是说
binary protocols
二进制协议
just imagine two systems or two teams
想象两个系统或两个团队
writing two pieces of software and they
编写两个软件，他们
don't call each other a lot there's not
不要互相打电话很多
a very tight interaction between them
他们之间非常紧密的互动
but they are both running on the same
但它们都在同一台上运行
database accessing the same tables in
数据库访问中的相同表
the same schema and what enter on and so
相同的架构以及输入内容等等
forth and even if you go for a modern
向前，即使你去现代
concept such as the main event and if
主要事件等概念以及
you have domain events that carry a lot
您有很多领域事件
of stuff with them and a lot of let's
与他们在一起的东西，还有很多
say a very big model in them I think
我想在他们身上说一个很大的模型
there is also
也有
a chance that you couple each to
你们每个人都有机会
applications on events so closely it can
事件上的应用程序是如此紧密
basically say there is a shared current
基本上说存在共享电流
between the two now in my eyes did you
在我眼中的两个之间
need to differentiate it if this is very
如果这非常需要区分它
bad or it can be tolerated let's be
不好或者可以容忍
honest I mean I see it always a
老实说，我总是看到
collection of trade-off decisions there
在那里收集权衡决策
is never a perfect world no matter where
永远都不是一个完美的世界
you look you always have trade-off
你看起来你总是在权衡
decision decision now if the two teams
现在决定如果两个团队决定
they success relies heavily on each
他们的成功很大程度上取决于每一个
other
其他
so both basically both succeeds and it's
所以两者基本上都成功了，
it's all good when you can send me this
可以寄给我这一切都很好
can be tolerated in some sort of way but
可以以某种方式容忍，但
if that is not the case the shared
如果不是这种情况，则共享
kernel can be quite a toxic element
仁可能是一种有毒元素
another thing is let's say one team
另一件事是说一个团队
provides a service for another team and
为另一个团队提供服务
the other team is calling the service
另一个团队正在致电服务
and we have a customer-supplier
我们有一个客户供应商
relationship between the two teams in
两队之间的关系
this case the downstream team which is
在这种情况下，下游团队
the consuming team and is playing a very
消耗队，并且正在打一场
dominant role in the organization or in
在组织或组织中的主导作用
this let's say with interaction between
这可以说与
the two teams so basically they can have
这两个团队基本上可以拥有
a veto right and that is something that
否决权，那就是
you usually do not see in the code if
您通常在代码中看不到
you take if you do an analysis of these
如果您对这些进行分析，
systems maybe you want to activation Hey
系统可能要激活嘿
how did the last interface change or the
最后一个界面如何更改，或者
last model change go down with the other
最后一个模型更改与另一个
team when they say oh don't mention that
团队，当他们说哦，别说那
the the boss of the other team went
另一个团队的老板去了
crazy he went not escalated it
疯了，他没有升级
throughout the complete organization and
在整个组织中
we have to pull it back there is a
我们必须把它拉回来
strong indication that you may
有力的迹象表明你可能
eventually have a custom of supplier
最终有供应商的习惯
relationship between the teams and same
团队之间的关系
scenario but totally different behavior
场景，但行为完全不同
is the component
是组件
in this case the downstream team which
在这种情况下，下游团队
is the consuming team basically conforms
消费团队基本符合吗
to the model of the upstream team and
上游团队的模型
there is basically no big translation of
基本上没有大的翻译
the model and also no vectoring so they
模型，也没有向量化，所以他们
have a very let's say defensive role in
可以说，在
the organization they take whatever they
他们采取的组织
want and this can be you to let's say
想要，这可以让你说
political power in organizations that
组织中的政治权力
can be the king but it can also be the
可以是国王，但也可以是国王
case when you just go ahead and take a
如果您只是继续前进并采取
model and yeah it's and you copy the
模型，是的，您复制了
model for instance I want to ran
例如我要运行的模型
personally into a very bad component
亲自成为一个非常糟糕的组成部分
situation I'm running a online music
我正在运行在线音乐的情况
magazine for heavy rock music and let's
杂志，重摇滚音乐，让我们
be honest displaying two days is very
老实说两天很
thrilling for a team that is providing
为正在提供的团队而激动
such a negative so we looked into
如此消极，所以我们调查了
website and whatever that provided tour
网站以及提供导览的任何内容
dates and there was one site that was
日期，有一个网站是
really fantastic they had a good API
真的很棒，他们有一个很好的API
good a good offering for systems writing
提供系统编写的好产品
code on top of the API and we went with
API上的代码，我们选择了
them and we totally confirmed to them in
他们，我们完全向他们证实
our internal model so basically the
我们的内部模型基本上
database was more left and after than
数据库的余留时间比
the UI layer was modeled after them it
UI层是根据它们建模的
was above in the first run it was great
在第一轮中就在上面，很棒
but then firmly they stopped the service
但后来他们坚定地停止了服务
I mean I couldn't pick up the phone and
我的意思是我无法接电话，
complain to them because maybe they've
向他们抱怨，因为也许他们已经
just shut my call down but we're stuck
只是关闭了我的电话，但我们被困
basically without today but being a
基本上没有今天，但成为
total conformist to another external
完全符合另一个外部
model and then we looked into different
模型，然后我们研究了不同的
other offerings and we found that one
其他产品，我们发现
and we have to take a decision okay do
我们必须做一个决定好吗
we rewrite our whole code do you realize
我们重写了整个代码，您知道吗
the whole system because we were so much
整个系统，因为我们是如此
conforming to the other model but
符合其他模型，但
basically we like the model it is model
基本上我们喜欢模型
two days and secular to resemble a
两天，世俗的像
really well so we decided no let's
真的很好，所以我们决定不让我们
define that is our new internal model
定义那是我们的新内部模型
and go with an anti-corruption basically
并基本上进行反腐败
an anti-corruption is and Leia or even a
反腐败是Leia甚至是
micro service that isolates a client
隔离客户端的微服务
model from another systems model by
来自另一个系统模型的模型
translation and you can i in my eyes you
翻译，你可以在我的眼中吗
can see an anti-corruption layer as
可以看到一个反腐败层
let's say a a simple mapping layer in a
假设一个简单的映射层
piece of code you could also go ahead
您也可以继续执行一段代码
and really for instance if you have a
举例来说，如果您有一个
lot of legacy applications in your
您的许多旧版应用程序
organization you can see that as a
组织，您可以将其视为
gateway to a more dynamic part of the IP
通往IP更动态部分的网关
in your organization and right let's say
在您的组织中，可以说
I call them anti-corruption micro
我称它们为反腐败微
services or something like that but for
服务或类似的东西，但为了
instance are able to consume the main
实例能够消耗主要
events and whatever and something that
事件以及其他任何东西
we actually want to do with our micro
我们实际上想与我们的微型
service idea and with cloud native
服务理念和云原生
applications or self-contained systems
应用程序或独立系统
is that if we don't see a lot of
就是如果我们看不到很多
connection between the boundary context
边界上下文之间的联系
of the system so every team can find
系统的每个团队都可以找到
their own solution to their domain um so
他们自己对自己域的解决方案，所以
there's basically one case where the
基本上有一种情况
team's really don't have any contact
团队真的没有任何联系
point to each other
指向对方
Tanna but i would say that you also have
坦娜，但我想你也有
to see how you get along with separate
看看你如何与单独相处
ways for instance if you have a very
例如，如果您有一个非常
domain event event based system you may
您可以基于域事件事件系统
eventually go ahead and rate that as
最终继续进行评分
separate ways as well I'll get to that
分开的方式我也会
later on the last two are let's say
接下来的两个让我们说
[Music]
[音乐]
important yes but not as central and the
重要的是，但不如中央和
other one the OPA host servers basically
其他一台OPA主机服务器
says is one context delivers
说是一种环境
functionality to other systems through a
通过其他系统的功能
exposing through an interface of
通过接口暴露
something so if you have a rest
这样的话，如果你休息一下
interface and micro service Lex
界面和微服务Lex
in defense or something that can be
在防御或可能是
rated as an open hole services is
被评为“裸眼服务”是
usually a model for the upstream system
通常是上游系统的模型
so the providing systems systems
所以提供系统
providing the functionality the
提供功能
published language is something that you
您发布的语言是您所需要的
usually have on your own poster so if
通常有自己的海报，所以如果
every model that you give out we publish
您发布的每个模型我们都会发布
a certain part of the language to other
语言的某些部分
to other systems to other contexts and
到其他系统到其他环境
please don't overdo the published
请不要过度发表
language kind of thing I already see a
语言的东西我已经看到了
couple of people who are still fans of
几个仍然是粉丝的人
the centralized company-wide data model
集中式公司范围内的数据模型
and they say oh great idea let's do a
他们说哦，好主意，让我们做一个
centralized published language no don't
集中发布的语言否请勿
do that you will be missing the point of
这样做，您将失去重点
it and now let's say why is that so
现在，让我们说为什么
interesting let's take a look at at this
有趣的让我们看看这个
system here and so for instance we have
系统在这里，例如，我们有
a mortgage or credit application and we
抵押或信贷申请，我们
we have the credit applications calling
我们有信贷申请电话
a CRM system where we have a customer if
拥有客户的CRM系统
a scoring system which is talking to a
与之对话的计分系统
credit agency we also have the creative
信贷机构，我们也有创意
decision context and that is something
决策环境，这就是
that a lot of you have already drawn out
你们很多人已经抽出
or sketched out in vml diagrams and
或在vml图中勾勒出
whatever context diagram however you
任何上下文图，但是你
want to see but here so far we only see
想看，但到目前为止，我们只看到
call back here and now let's add the
回这里，现在让我们添加
idea of context mapping to that picture
上下文映射到该图片的想法
now first of all we classify these the
现在我们首先将这些分类
upstream who's the downstream system
上游谁是下游系统
downstream is consuming system upstream
下游是消耗系统的上游
is the providing system why is it called
是提供系统的原因
like that take a look at a river I live
那样看我住的河
in your berth pad area and next to
在您的泊位垫区域内
nrnberg is a city called fruit and well
纽伦堡是个叫做水果和健康的城市
for instance if you see it in the US or
例如，如果您在美国看到它，或者
wherever to neighboring city
到邻近城市的任何地方
is always have a sort of rivalry between
总是之间存在某种竞争
them and between Nuremberg and third
他们以及纽伦堡和第三名之间
there is a river passing which is deep
有一条河经过深
Ignace and it's a tiny River another big
伊格纳斯，这是一条小河，又一条大河
thing like the Danube or whatever submit
诸如多瑙河之类的东西
and the river is flowing from Nuremberg
河流从纽伦堡流出
to trip so Nuremberg is upstream fruit
去旅行，所以纽伦堡是上游水果
is downstream
在下游
so if Nuremberg is putting a lot of
所以如果纽伦堡投入很多
waste into the river it flows down to
废物流入河流
fruit and the number this would say
水果和这个数字会说
where it belongs
它属于哪里
but joke aside approach it bouncing it
但开个玩笑的办法它反弹
can get the waste from from the upstream
可以从上游得到废物
and the same is with models if you have
如果你有模型的话
a crappy model in the upstream system it
上游系统中的cr脚模型
can propagate down to the downstream
可以向下传播到下游
system and make that model crap as well
系统，并使模型废话
now let's add from some examples on the
现在让我们从
context map for instance the credit
上下文地图，例如信用
agency the credit decision and the CRM
代理信用决策和CRM
or providing Omaha services so there is
或提供奥马哈服务，因此
a let's say there is a they provide some
假设有一个他们提供一些
interfaces for instance to Rath called
例如与Rath的接口称为
or less services or whatever now the
或更少的服务或现在
interesting part begins between scoring
有趣的部分开始于得分之间
and their credit application we have a
和他们的信用申请，我们有一个
shack Colonel these are very old school
小屋上校，这些都是很老的学校
applications they are still
他们仍然在申请
communicating with each other through
通过相互交流
our AMI
我们的AMI
so there is a strong shackle now between
所以现在之间有很强的束缚
the credit agency and scoring yes a
信用社，是
conformance on the scoring cycle but the
符合得分周​​期，但
scoring founded context is confirming a
对已建立的上下文评分正在确认
lot to the model of the credit agency
信贷机构的模式很多
which it is consuming and the credit
它正在消耗和信誉
application has a very bossy boss and
应用程序的老板非常专横，
he's always fighting with the credit
他一直在努力争取信誉
decision team making this a customer
决策团队使其成为客户
supplier relationship whereas we have an
供应商关系，而我们有一个
anti-corruption there between the CRM
CRM之间存在反腐败
system and the credit application
系统和信用申请
the interesting part here we see if the
有趣的部分在这里，我们看看
way from the credit agency to scoring to
从信贷机构到评分的方式
the credit application
信贷申请
please take a close look here scoring is
请仔细看这里的得分是
conforming to the credit agency credit
符合信用社信用
application has a shared kernel with
应用程序具有与
scoring so there is a champ or a big
得分，所以会有冠军或大个子
risk the basically parts of the model of
冒险模型的基本部分
the credit agency are flowing down into
信贷机构正流入
the credit application so if you want to
信用申请，因此，如果您想
switch the credit agency for instance in
切换信贷机构，例如
Germany we have a couple of these
德国，我们有几个
one is the shootout the other one is
一个是枪战，另一个是
info score if you want to switch from
信息分数，如果您想从
shooter to input score for instance your
射手输入分数，例如您的
first assumption on the enterprise model
企业模型的第一个假设
will be ha no big deal
没什么大不了的
let's just change the code in the
让我们只更改其中的代码
scoring and meet into the project
得分并参加项目
somebody realated you mean odd then
有人意识到你的意思是奇怪
we're in trouble
我们有麻烦了
we also have to adjust the credit
我们还必须调整信用额度
etiquette and these are very valuable
礼节和这些非常有价值
insights that you gain and now so far
您到目前为止获得的见解
for the theory let's take a look into
对于理论，我们来看看
the practice I promise it's not going to
我保证不会的做法
be a packed shop this park owned the
成为这个公园拥有的打包商店
bank and he's giving out loans it's
银行，他正在发放贷款
called big problem and this is an
叫做大问题，这是一个
application that is running on Cloud
在云上运行的应用程序
Foundry so basically this is an
铸造厂，基本上这是一个
application which I'm hosting right now
我现在正在托管的应用程序
on on the public cloud foundry and
在公共云铸造厂上
there's a credit agency credit
有信用社信用
application customer micro service some
应用客户微服务的一些
customer contact kind of thing and a
客户联系的东西和
scoring engine and if we click through
计分引擎，如果我们点击进入
this we can basically apply for a loan
这基本上可以申请贷款
let's say 12 months 2000 or 1200 euros
假设12个月2000或1200欧元
purpose a new park and we're an income
打算建一个新公园，我们就是收入
let's say the person earns 4000 euros no
假设这个人的收入是4000欧元
rental income but they have to pay 1500
租金收入，但他们必须支付1500
for rent and 300 for loan repayments and
租金和还款300
let's say another 400 for cost of living
比方说另外400美元的生活费用
now after that we can
现在之后，我们可以
shop with some customer details first
首先购买一些客户详细信息
name is michael fluid Kreutz grungy 11
名字叫迈克尔·弗洛伊德Kreutz grungy 11
is 83 t1 mentioned which is our in OQ
提到的是83 t1
office in Munich so we're going to come
慕尼黑办事处，所以我们要来
by and say hi to that and then we
然后对这个打个招呼，然后我们
perform a scoring of this and this is
对此进行评分，这是
basically the process that we are
基本上是我们的过程
running through now
现在运行
so obviously the talk says yes I
所以很明显，谈话说我
financed the purchase of new pucks very
非常资助购买新冰球
good
好
go ahead all policy use and let's take a
继续使用所有政策，让我们
look at the code now and imagine a
现在看一下代码，想象一下
context magnetically what we see here is
磁性的上下文，我们在这里看到的是
we have a couple of sprinkled
我们有几洒
applications the credit agency the
申请信贷机构
credit application the customer customer
信用申请客户客户
context scoring incurring shared code
上下文评分产生共享代码
and this is not a spring boot back
这不是 spring boot
practice application please be aware
练习申请请注意
that I have added and you will see that
我添加的内容，您将看到
a couple of nasty things in there the
那里有几个讨厌的东西
first thing is I put a lot of logic into
首先是我投入了很多逻辑
my controller because I want to make it
我的控制器，因为我想做到
easy for you to follow it up in your
方便您在自己的帐户中进行后续操作
code obviously for a production system I
显然是为生产系统编写代码
would handle these kinds of things
会处理这类事情
differently
不同地
I've also switched out all the spring
我整个 Spring 都关门了
cloud goodness so no oil a car history
云的好处，所以没有油汽车历史
or whatever I really want to focus on
或我真正想关注的任何事情
the BDD court here now the first step is
BDD法院现在的第一步是
after the first page we go ahead and
在第一页之后，我们继续
basically save the credit application to
基本上将信用申请保存到
the repository of the credit application
信用申请的存储库
here so going back there basically what
在这里，所以基本上回到那里
I what I have here is very similar let's
我在这里的东西非常相似，让我们
make that a bit bigger
使它更大
oops that's too big just the size yeah
哎呀，太大了，只是大小
not better so basically we stay in
不好，所以基本上我们留在
in this credit application thing now in
现在在这个信用申请中
the second step we go ahead and interact
第二步，我们进行互动
with some customer client so we called
与一些客户客户，所以我们打电话给
some input from for the customer and we
来自客户的一些意见，我们
are now directing this one to the
现在正在将这个指向
customer system here now the customer
客户系统现在是客户
client in the credit application take a
信用申请中的客户
look at that patient work looks like
看着病人的工作看起来像
that and what we see here is we have a
那，我们在这里看到的是，我们有一个
public web service model from the WSDL
WSDL中的公共Web服务模型
from customer and we were mapping our
来自客户，我们正在绘制我们的地图
own customer to the client to the
自己的客户到客户的
upstream customer in this case it's a
在这种情况下，上游客户是
one-to-one mapping so either we could
一对一映射，所以我们可以
say huh we have a conformance in or we
说吧，我们符合
have an anti-corruption there since it
从那以后开始反腐败
is isolated here I would rate that as an
被隔离在这里，我将其评为
anti-corruption layer between the
之间的反腐败层
customer system and the credit
客户系统和信誉
application at the customer system is
客户系统上的应用程序是
also providing an open whole service
还提供开放的整体服务
because it has a lesser significant
因为它的重要性较低
export and we you jump over to the
出口，我们您跳到了
scoring thing so we interact with our
得分的东西，所以我们与我们的互动
own code and we go ahead and perform
自己的代码，我们继续执行
from scoring on this thing so there is
从这个东西上得分，所以有
an interface called scoring input and
称为评分输入和
the scoring service performs the scoring
计分服务执行计分
now what is this scoring service about
现在这个计分服务是关于什么的
now where is that located we see the
现在在哪里，我们看到了
scoring service is located in the
计分服务位于
scoring shared crandall change also the
为共享的crandall变化评分
scoring input class some agency color
给输入类别打分一些代理商颜色
and whatnot
还有什么
let's take a look at the configuration
让我们看一下配置
there is an integration on a binary
在二进制文件上有一个集成
level between the credit application and
信贷申请与
the score
比分
application because we're communicating
应用程序，因为我们正在沟通
with each other through Hessian a Chien
通过黑森州的钱
for those of you who don't know it is an
对于那些不知道这是一个
HTTP based binary protocol which is also
基于HTTP的二进制协议
supported by our beloved spring-trap
由我们钟爱的Spring 夹支持
books so you also have an integration
书，所以你也有一个整合
interaction for spring application
Spring 应用交互
actually for a binary protocol pretty
实际上对于一个二进制协议
high performance I would prepare it at
高性能，我会在
any time or a Mayan stuff so but what we
任何时候或玛雅的东西，但我们
have between the scoring and the credit
在得分和信用之间
application is a ship kernel between the
应用程序是
two and as you can see there is another
两个，如您所见，还有另一个
jump to the credit agency over there now
现在跳到那边的信用社
let's jump right into the scoring
让我们直接进入得分
application and go ahead and take a look
应用程序，继续看一下
at the scoring service what's happening
在计分服务中发生了什么事
right there is we perform of scoring
正确的是我们进行计分
it's a rest call obviously HTTP entity
这是一个REST呼叫，显然是HTTP实体
Springs retrograde and so on and so
Spring 逆行等等
forth and we get an agency record the
第四，我们得到一个代理商记录
agency result is something we get from
代理结果是我们从中得到的
the response body and it is something
响应主体，这是
that we directly or more or less return
我们直接或多或少的回报
directly to the result over through the
直接通过
share come to the credit application
分享到信用申请
here I mean there's a couple of reasons
在这里我的意思是有两个原因
the process if the reason for the loan
贷款原因的过程
contains the word talk it's a big bonus
包含“说话”这个词是很大的收获
otherwise you'll be screwed by him but
否则你会被他搞砸，但是
the interesting thing is here and
有趣的事情在这里
obviously we are absolutely conforming
显然，我们绝对合规
in this service to the model of the
在此服务的模型
credit agency so we have a conformist
信贷机构，所以我们有一个顺从者
here and in this example what we see
在这个例子中，我们看到的是
here take please take a close look to
这里请仔细看一下
the agency record in the credit
信用证中的代理商记录
application controller down there we
我们下面的应用程序控制器
pass the scoring results to buy
通过评分结果购买
and we see the agency record right in
我们看到代理商记录就在
the UI so basically if you switch the
用户界面，所以基本上，如果您切换
credit agency they have a different
信用社，他们有不同的
model for their records and whatever you
为他们的记录和您所用的模型
will I would say run into this big
我会说碰到这么大
trouble because you have to adjust the
麻烦，因为您必须调整
credit education as well now you may
现在也可以进行学分教育
have wondered what is this customer
想知道这位顾客是什么
contact all about we haven't talked
联系我们所有尚未谈论的内容
about that yet so far we have address
关于这一点，到目前为止，我们有地址
this way we have the customer the credit
这样，我们就获得了客户的信任
application scoring the credit agency
对信用机构评分的申请
and so on now the customer context comes
依此类推，现在有了客户环境
into play here let's take a look at the
让我们来看看
customer application for instance after
客户申请之后
saving a customer we publish and domain
保存我们发布的客户并确定域
event a customer created event and we
客户创建的事件，我们
send it through ready
通过准备发送
through the ready pops up feature which
通过准备弹出功能
is also supported by spring data for
的Spring 数据也支持
Eddy's thank you why did I use Redis I
艾迪谢谢你为什么我要用Redis
didn't use rather than cue I say reddit
没有使用而不是暗示我说reddit
reddit is very easy to install a lot of
reddit很容易安装很多
developers have it already running on
开发人员已经在运行它
the machine and I wanted to make it very
这台机器，我想使其非常
easy for you folks to try out these
方便您尝试这些
examples here so that's the reason
这里的例子，这就是原因
perennis and that for using reddit and
perennis以及使用reddit和
cue or something like that
提示或类似的东西
and and in the customer context what we
在客户方面，我们
have here is a part we go ahead and we
这是我们前进的一部分，我们
have a list even for the customer
甚至有一份客户清单
created event what we do here we have
创建事件我们在这里做什么
our own customer created event in the
我们自己的客户在
customer context thing and it is able to
客户上下文的东西，它能够
come convert create a customer to an
来将客户创建为
address and we're going to say that
地址，我们要说的是
address to our own repository so here we
地址到我们自己的存储库，所以在这里我们
are working with eventually consistency
正在最终保持一致
and with a very decentralized approach
并且采用非常分散的方法
to seeing models on the one context it's
在一个环境中查看模型
a customer the under context
上下文中的客户
it's basically an address and in the end
它基本上是一个地址，最后
of the credit application controllers
信贷申请控制者
level we're sending out for instance and
例如，我们发送的级别
credit application approved event and
信贷申请批准事件和
this event is being consumed by the
该事件正在被
credit application approved event reseda
信贷申请批准的事件摘要
and what we do is we go ahead and look
我们要做的是继续前进
for an address in this case and send it
在这种情况下发送地址并发送
a fake letter which is basically ending
假信基本上已经结束
up in the Lafayette I'm not going to
在拉斐特，我不会
print out a letter whatever so this is
无论如何打印出一封信
something and we're a few teams might
什么，我们是几个团队
discuss and that can be some sort of a
讨论，这可能是某种
share of a separate way because there is
分享一种单独的方式，因为
a very loose coupling between for
之间的非常松散的耦合
instance the customer the customer
实例客户客户
contact or the credit application and
联系人或信用申请以及
the customer contact person I would say
我要说的客户联系人
make an a decision in your team how you
在团队中做出决定
want to raise that I would say rating
想提高我的评价
that as the sort of four separate ways
作为四种单独的方式
it's fair enough is it
这是公平的
academically a hundred percent correct
学术上正确的百分之一百
I wouldn't I wouldn't say that but I
我不会，我不会那样说，但我
think it is a very high degree of loose
认为这是一个很高的松散度
coupling that we have here now that's it
现在我们在这里拥有的耦合就是这样
with the application I suggest I'll
我建议使用该应用程序
share all the slides online you can also
在线共享所有幻灯片，您也可以
check out the project on github and now
在github上检查项目，现在
my card here is over you can still
我的卡在这里了，你仍然可以
follow me on twitter at the post and if
在帖子上在Twitter上关注我，如果
you're interested in DTD training or
您对DTD培训感兴趣或
consulting also with a focus on
咨询也着重于
everything around spring you can contact
您可以联系 Spring 周围的一切
me and I would like to hand over to our
我和我想移交给我们
awesome host Peter also like Michael I
很棒的主持人Peter也喜欢Michael I
want to share a couple of things with
想要与他人分享一些东西
you yeah so on
你是这样
real quick just to finish off before we
真正快才结束
do some questions and answer if you
做一些问题并回答，如果你
could go to the last slide Michael add a
可以转到迈克尔最后一张幻灯片
couple things I want to have to pour
我想倒的几件事
watt through the whole thing
瓦特贯穿整个事情
gotcha okay while you're doing that yeah
知道了，当您这样做时，是的
let's go ahead and ask some questions
让我们继续问一些问题
that you've collected from the audience
从观众那里收集的
yeah no problem no problem so real quick
是的，没问题，没问题，这么快
folks on the replay will show up on a
重播的人将显示在
pivotal website as well as the spring
关键的网站以及 Spring
YouTube channel and so there should be
YouTube频道，所以应该有
an announcement showing on your screen
屏幕上显示一条公告
right now that has links to both the
现在有链接到
where we post the replays on the pivotal
我们将重播发布到关键
website and as well as a shortcut to the
网站以及快捷方式
Spring YouTube channel and then all you
春季YouTube频道，然后您
need to do is look for the webinars
需要做的是寻找网络研讨会
playlist so generally with the system
播放列表通常与系统配合使用
we're using these days the webinars will
这些天，我们将使用网络研讨会
go right to the pivotal website same day
当天直接访问关键网站
the replays and then it'll just take us
重播，然后带我们
a day or two to get it up on the YouTube
一两天就能在YouTube上使用
channel the nice thing about the pivotal
引导有关关键的事情
website is that there is a whole bunch
网站是一堆
of other spring related content that is
其他与春季相关的内容是
not on spring dot IO so if you're
不在spring dot IO上，所以如果你是
looking for more content on on spring
在春季寻找更多内容
and a potentially wider perspective
以及更广阔的前景
there's a whole bunch of other stuff on
还有很多其他的东西
the pivotal website that that is
关键的网站
exclusive and isn't on the spring
独家，不是 Spring
website so I highly recommend you check
网站，因此我强烈建议您检查
that out on a lot of it's sort of spring
在很多 Spring 里
boot related or running spring on a
引导相关或正在运行的Spring
cloud and that sort of thing also we
云之类的东西，我们
would love to have you come back and
很想让你回来，
join us on April 13th on Nicholas funk
4月13日加入我们，参加Nicholas Funk
hell from Hybris frequence bring one
Hybris地狱带来的地狱
presenter and spring enthusiasts among
主持人和春季发烧友
other things he's going to be doing a
他要做的其他事情
sort of Josh long style talk about how
约什（Josh）的长风格谈论如何
spring boot works under the hood so if
spring boot 在引擎盖下工作，所以如果
you are you know thinking about doing
你知道你在考虑做
micro services and applying some of
微服务和一些应用
these domain-driven concepts that
这些领域驱动的概念
michael has been talking about today and
迈克尔今天一直在谈论
using spring cloud and spring boots
使用Spring 云和 spring boot
you'll probably want to know at some
您可能想知道一些
point how to go past the the intelligent
指出如何超越智能
defaults and maybe do that sort of next
默认值，也许下一步
level of debugging so highly recommend
调试级别如此强烈推荐
you check that out and register it
您检查并注册
sounds like also
听起来也
had some firewall issue today that
今天有一些防火墙问题
people that can't get past that can't
无法超越的人
allow our MTP protocol we're having
允许我们拥有的MTP协议
trouble with the webinars or something
网络研讨会或其他问题
to keep in mind last thing is for folks
要记住最后一件事是给人们的
that are looking for for training and
正在寻找培训和
certification obviously it sounds like
认证显然听起来像
noq is offering some very specific
noq提供了一些非常具体的
courses around domain driven but
围绕领域驱动的课程，但
strategic domain driven design and and
战略领域驱动的设计和
other things that i think are fantastic
我认为其他很棒的事情
if you're looking for more product
如果您正在寻找更多产品
oriented training they're there that is
定向培训，他们在那里
something you can can also get from
你也可以从中得到的东西
pivotal you know comes in a number of
你知道的关键是很多
flavors and various instructor-led live
口味和各种讲师指导的现场
online e-learning and you can see there
在线电子学习，您可以在那里看到
a little bit about what we're offering
关于我们提供的内容
in terms of you know just sort of course
就您而言，当然
spring you know certification track the
Spring 你知道认证跟踪
enterprise integration kind of using
企业整合的一种使用
spring integration and those sorts of
Spring Integration 以及诸如此类的
things on as well as eventually getting
事情以及最终得到
to things like spring cloud on and for
对于像 Spring Cloud 这样的事情
microservice product training so those
微服务产品培训
are all available on the website on if
都可以在网站上找到
you go to the pivotal website and look
你去关键的网站，看看
for education training certification you
为了教育培训证书你
can find that there's also links to it
可以发现那里也有链接
on the spring website in the footer so
在春季网站的页脚中
with that thanks for for listening
感谢您的收听
let's get into a couple of questions had
让我们进入几个问题
a bunch of good ones I'm going to
一堆好东西，我要去
actually start with the longest question
实际上是从最长的问题开始
seeing as we don't have too many too
看到我们没有太多
much time Michael one one of the
很多时间迈克尔之一
attendees asks what is the right level
与会者问什么是正确的水平
of granularity when defining and
定义和
decomposing bounded contexts in the
分解边界上下文
online shopping experience is commerce
网上购物经验是商业
or purchase product a good boundary
或购买产品有良好的边界
definition for a bounded context we're
我们在有限范围内的定义
decomposing it to like shop browsing
分解成类似于商店浏览
catalog cart management order creation
目录购物车管理订单创建
payment order fulfillment all a separate
付款单履行全部分开
bounded context unto themselves like how
对自己的有限上下文就像
fine brain you know do you do you advise
大脑好，你知道吗？
people to look at doing this yeah there
人们看做这个耶
is indeed a really great question and
确实是一个非常好的问题，
thanks for bringing that up because this
感谢您提出来，因为这
is a question that okay a lot of my
这个问题我很多
clients or discussing a lot and in my
客户或讨论很多，在我
eyes
眼睛
one there is no perfect recipe for that
一个没有完美的配方
but I let me come up with a couple of
但我让我提出几个
questions you should ask yourself when
你什么时候应该问自己的问题
modeling it and if you have a context
对其进行建模以及是否有上下文
that can't be managed by one team alone
不能仅由一个团队来管理
if it's just today that they need two
如果只是今天他们需要两个
three or four teams I would go ahead and
三四支球队，我会继续前进，
split it up the first rule I would
把它分解成我会的第一条规则
always say one context one team that's
总是说一个背景一个团队
the first thing that I would bring to
我要带给的第一件事
the table recording them the next is and
记录下一个的表是
I would go into the discussion with my
我会和我一起讨论
domain experts experts on that I would
领域专家专家，我会
discuss with my business people how they
与我的商人讨论他们如何
see their business where they see
在他们看到的地方看到他们的生意
relations between contexts where they
它们之间的上下文之间的关系
say okay this is extremely similar there
说好吧，那里非常相似
is a very high degree of cohesion
凝聚力很高
between among the business use or there
之间的业务使用或那里
isn't a high degree of cohesion between
两者之间的凝聚力不是很高
those if you if you don't have high
如果你没有高的话
degree on cohesion here I would split it
凝聚力的程度在这里我会拆分
up so given the example that that has
因此给出的例子
been written here I would tend to a
在这里写，我倾向于
rousing cut off cart management or a
唤醒中断的购物车管理或
creation payment or the person and and
创作付款或个人以及
so on if you look at a lot of e-commerce
如果你看很多电子商务的话
applications and you you will be like
应用程序，您会像
that these are by themselves actually
这些都是他们自己
already quite big contests and I
已经相当大的比赛，我
wouldn't go extremely finally granular
最终不会变得非常细
on that a likely there is a a concept
关于这可能有一个概念
called a self-contained system which in
称为一个独立的系统
my eyes fits absolutely perfect on the
我的眼睛绝对适合
view on a micro service you can write
您可以在微服务上查看
with spring --beautiful instance and
Spring -美丽的实例和
there is a website called SES
有一个名为SES的网站
architecture that org and I would highly
该组织和我会高度重视
recommend you to
推荐你
take a look here in order to get a
在这里看看，以获得一个
little bit of input on how to model
关于如何建模的一点点投入
these self-contained systems under
这些独立的系统
context cool yeah I've seen you guys
上下文很酷，是的，我见过你们
tweeting about that I've been meaning to
在推特上说我一直在意
read that myself and make sure I get a
自己读一遍，确保我得到一个
get a handle on what you what you're
掌握您所处的状态
talking about there cool I think that
谈论那里很酷，我认为
also kind of answers the second part of
也有点答案的第二部分
the question is is that that gentleman
问题是那个绅士
had about how founded context map to
关于如何建立上下文映射到
domain own or shape like the sort of
领域拥有或形状像
people delivery you know where you were
人们送货，你知道你在哪里
talking about it so yeah um there's a
谈论它，所以是的，有一个
bunch of other questions so I'm gonna
一堆其他问题，我要
try let me ask let me add one more thing
尝试让我问一下，让我再添加一件事
to that domain ownership is for one
该域所有权是一个
context and I always say that hops is
我总是说啤酒花是
one thing is absolutely perfect if you
一件事绝对是完美的，如果你
can also have a domain person in your
您也可以有一个域人
team as well that's a good point I will
团队也很重要，我会
be there perfect yeah another other
在那里完美吗，另一个
aspect to a balanced team there along
一个平衡的团队
with you know product management and QA
知道产品管理和质量检查
and the developer yep absolutely that's
开发人员是的，绝对是
a great that's a great that's a good
一个伟大的一个伟大的一个很好的
idea on so just folks this system is
这样的想法，只是这个人是
going to cut us off at four minutes ft
将在四分钟英尺处切断我们
hours so that's literally all the time
几个小时
we have for questions so it's not that
我们有问题要问，不是
we don't want to answer them in fact
我们实际上不想回答他们
what we're planning what we'd like to do
我们正在计划要做什么
is if any questions if you ask a
是如果您问一个问题
question and we don't get to it we are
问题，我们不明白，我们是
going to publish Michael's answers to
将要发布迈克尔的答案
those questions as attachments to the
这些问题作为附件
webinar replay on the pivotal website
关键网站上的网络研讨会重播
so again go get that link that's
所以再次去获得那个链接
displaying in the announcement right now
现在显示在公告中
content up fizzled i/o forward slash
满足于失败的I / O正斜杠
webinars and then if your question did
网络研讨会，然后如果您的问题做了
not get answered we will type out an
没有得到答案，我们将输入
answer to that and put it into that put
回答并放入那个
it into the put it into the replay as an
它放到重播中作为
attachment um so with that I think
依，我想
there's there's one other question I
我还有一个问题
think is really good on that it kind of
认为这真的很不错
relates to what we were just talking
与我们刚才所说的有关
about gentleman asks um does it mean if
关于绅士问嗯，这是否意味着
services shared the database and code
服务共享数据库和代码
are they really not that independent
他们真的不是那么独立吗
should have shared kernel be used
应该使用共享内核
carefully with micro services for that
仔细地使用微服务
reason and are there any good rules of
原因，是否有任何良好的规则
thumb when to use a shell kernel I
拇指什么时候使用shell内核我
really like that question that's great
真的很喜欢那个问题
yeah
是的
great question absolutely great um I
很好的问题，绝对很好，我
would say in the moment that services
会在那一刻说
share the database and code they are
共享数据库和代码
getting more tightly coupled to each
越来越紧密地耦合到每个
other that the first step to tie the
其他的第一步
coupling and it goes up here sooner or
耦合，它早点在这里上升或
later end up in discussion so we concept
后来结束讨论，所以我们概念
service a life without updating service
无需更新服务就能生活
B and the only reason I can I could for
B，也是我能做到的唯一原因
instance a little dab is if these teams
举例来说，如果这些团队
their success really depends on on each
他们的成功取决于每个人
other okay so one more question
其他还好，还有一个问题
one minute Peter be quick literally I
彼得一分钟快一点我
think we have like it's for 45 seconds
认为我们喜欢45秒
left
剩下
I think we should kind of I think we
我认为我们应该
need to leave it at that I'm going to
需要把它留在我要去的地方
dress one or two things people were
给人们穿一两件衣服
asking for on the link to the website
在网站链接上询问
which handles the domain architecture as
将域架构作为
well as the github repo for the code you
以及代码的github回购
were showing and we will put those is it
正在显示，我们将放置这些
okay if we put those into the absolutely
好吧，如果我们把那些放到绝对
attachment absolutely okay yeah bye
附件绝对好，是的，再见
folks of lt new attachment that will be
人们将获得新的依恋
in the attachment and those will be that
在附件中，这些将是
will be published later today on that
将于今天晚些时候发布
bright talk channel at the the URL the
URL上的直播频道
content up Hilda are you Oh URL thank
希尔达（Hilda）满意吗URL谢谢
you so much Michael really appreciate
迈克尔非常感谢你
your time your attention your your
你的时间你的注意力你
presentation and
介绍和